<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Simon Sure</title>
    <link>https://simonsure.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Simon Sure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://simonsure.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hackathons 2024</title>
      <link>https://simonsure.com/posts/2024/hackathons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonsure.com/posts/2024/hackathons/</guid>
      <description>This covers my current hackathon plan until the end of June. If you&amp;rsquo;re also participating in one of the envents, please send me a message; I would love to conenct beforehand!&#xA;ETHTallinn, Tallinn, Estonia (19. April - 21. April) ZEISS Computer Vision Hackathon: Reveal the Invisible, Karlsruhe, Germany (26. April - 28. April) EUDIS Hackathon, Milan, Italy (31. May - 2. June) The list will hopefully be extended with time. 🙂</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polykum: In der Schweiz</title>
      <link>https://simonsure.com/posts/2024/article-in-der-schweiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonsure.com/posts/2024/article-in-der-schweiz/</guid>
      <description>Meine Motivation für den Weg in die Schweiz war nicht die Schweiz als Land, sondern der Ruf der ETH. Vor meinem Umzug hatte ich mich nie ernsthaft gesellschaftlich mit meinem neuen Wohnland auseinandergesetzt. Ich habe unreflektiert und ignorant angenommen, dass die Unterschiede zu Deutschland nicht gigantisch sein würden und deshalb keinen Kulturschock erwartet. Doch je länger ich hier lebe, desto deutlicher werden die Unterschiede. An der ETH und im akademischen Umfeld allgemein sind diese Besonderheiten allerdings weniger ausgeprägt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polykum: Moving Machines</title>
      <link>https://simonsure.com/posts/2024/article-moving-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonsure.com/posts/2024/article-moving-machines/</guid>
      <description>Most robots are built to efficiently fulfil specified tasks — industrial robots being the clear example. Yet robots can also accomplishing fascinating movements and may only find a specific commercial application in the future, if ever. To create this unique movement, engineers often draw inspiration from animals, humans, and fiction.&#xA;Automata have a long history. One could argue that contributions from Alexandrian engineers to hydraulics — movement effected by exerting pressure on incompressible fluids— and pneumatics — movement effected by exerting pressure on gases— started the development of what one might consider robots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Season 2023</title>
      <link>https://simonsure.com/posts/2023/season-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonsure.com/posts/2023/season-2023/</guid>
      <description>https://www.instagram.com/reel/C1iHzUToPzK/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;igsh=MzRlODBiNWFlZA==&#xA;https://youtu.be/qZgWbL8bKUs</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
