<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simon Sure</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Simon Sure</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ETHTallinn 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/events/ethtallinn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/events/ethtallinn/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn Text&#xA;missing YT-Short LinkedIn X/Twitter </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flowboarding April</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/flowboarding-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/flowboarding-april/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackathons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/events/hackathons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/events/hackathons/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting times ahead! In the coming weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ll be diving into a series of hackathons across Europe, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share the journey with you all. Each event presents a unique opportunity to learn, innovate, and connect with incredible people in the tech community.&#xA;🌍 First stop: ETHTallinn in Tallinn, Estonia (April 19-21). This marks my first ETH event experience. ETHTallinn is poised to be the most important event in the Baltics, uniting Ethereum enthusiasts to innovate on DeFi, NFT, and Web3 technologies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampere</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/travel/tampere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/travel/tampere/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teijo National Park</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/travel/teijo-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/travel/teijo-national-park/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuuksio National Park</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/travel/nuuksio-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/travel/nuuksio-national-park/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Season 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/season-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/season-2023/</guid>
      <description>Find my look back on Instagram or YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIZAR</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/projects/flizar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/projects/flizar/</guid>
      <description>FLIZAR originated with the Digital Seeds ideathon. Our project group formed in early-mid 2023 and since then we have worked hard on our platform.&#xA;FLIZAR enables students to prepare as effficient as possible for their exams (personalized to their specific course considering university and lecturer). This is possible by custom generating an unlimited amount of training materials for each student. The exercises include solutions and FLIZAR adapts to a learner&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field Robot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/projects/field-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/projects/field-robot/</guid>
      <description>With a team of varying size (2 to 5), we have worked on the Field Robot Development Project. I&amp;rsquo;ve been part of the project from 2019 to 2023.&#xA;The goal was to build a small, mobile agricultural robot for row crops such as corn. The robot ought to be fully autonomous (meaning no GPS, no cellular or other connectivity etc.). Our robot drive system based on a recycled hoverboard, whose motors we reused.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abitur</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/deprecated/2022/abitur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/deprecated/2022/abitur/</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of resources I created while preparing for my Abitur exams in 2022.&#xA;All information provided here is given without any guarantee!&#xA;Mathematics (intensive course) Link to heading You can find a script here.&#xA;Physics (intensive course) Link to heading You can find a script here.&#xA;German Link to heading To be completed. Files are available in /abitur/german/&#xA;Social Sciences Link to heading You can find a script here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my digital space! I&amp;rsquo;m Simon Sure, a tech enthusiast with a relentless drive for innovation, learning, and making a tangible impact. Immersed in the world of Computer Science at ETH Zurich, I&amp;rsquo;m not just a student; I&amp;rsquo;m a fervent explorer at the intersection of technology and real-world challenges. With an unyielding work ethic and drive, I&amp;rsquo;m always seeking new experiences and challenges to help me grow, both personally and professionally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code References</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/code-references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/code-references/</guid>
      <description> personal GitHub Agricultural Robot Development Project GitHub </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description> email info@simonsure.com (primary) simon.sure@inf.ethz.ch phone (texts/Signal/WhatsApp/Telegram): +41798724929 telegram: @simonsure meeting/talk socials Link to heading LinkedIn X/Twitter Mastodon Bluesky Threads WhatsApp Instagram GitHub </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHZ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ethz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ethz/</guid>
      <description>This prage provides an overview of study materials, which I create(d) during my studies. I do not take responsibility for correctness or completeness. If you have any questions or remarks, do not hesitate to send me a message.&#xA;You can find my notes from during each semester here. And below are polished summaries and cheat sheets.&#xA;3rd semester (HS23) Link to heading Numerical Methods for Computer Science Systems Programming and Computer Architecture Analysis 2 Cheat Sheet 2nd semester (FS23) Link to heading Parallel Programming Essentials Algorithms and Probability Essentials Digital Design and Computer Architecture Analysis 1 1st semester (HS22) Link to heading Algorithms and Data Structures Essentials Discrete Mathematics Cheat Sheet Linear Algebra cheat Sheet lecture recordings on YouTube Link to heading Numerical Methods for Computer Science - HS23 Analysis 2 - HS23 Theoretische Informatik - HS23 Systems Programming - HS23 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects-events/</guid>
      <description>This showcases some of the projects I have worked on in recent years. If you have any questions or want to learn more, please reach out.&#xA;While studying I provide my notes and preparation scripts online. You can find those here.&#xA;Also, I participate in and am always on the lookout for Hackathons (and other events). If you can recommand any hackathon or event (globally), please let me know.&#xA;Projects Link to heading FLIZAR Field Robot FloRaWAN Interactive Image Video Hackathons Link to heading Hackathons are great fun and I really enjoy getting a software ready in just a few hours or days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading/</guid>
      <description>Readings Ideas Link to heading non-fiction Link to heading The Making of Princeton Univeristy by James Axtell American History: A Very Short Introduction by Paul S. Boyer The Worlds I See: Curiosity, Exploration, and Discovery at the Dawn of AI by Fei-Fei Li Helsinki: A Cultural History by Neil Kent The Structure of Scientific Revolutions by Thomas S. Kuhn Meditations by Marcus Aurelius Modern World History by Dan Allosso &amp;amp; Tom Williford Invention and Innovation: A Brief History of Hype and Failure by Vaclav Smil How the World Really Works: A Scientist&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Our Past, Present and Future by Vaclav Smil general textbooks Link to heading Introduction to Linear Algebra by Gilbert Strang Introduction to Finance: Markets, Investments, and Financial Management by Ronald Melicher and Edgar Norton Quantitative Trading: How to Build Your Own Algorithmic Trading Business by Ernest P.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
